# Pei-Shan. Tsai (Karen)

# **Digital designer**



**Email** 



**Portfolio** 

https://www.peishandesign.com



LinkedIn

# Summary

Junior digital designer with a background in fashion design, offering two years of graphic design experience and one year focused on creating intuitive website experiences. Seeking opportunities to gain experience in various design areas, including UI/UX design, Website design, Graphic design, and more.

## **Education**

# **University of Technology Sydney**

Master Degree in Interaction Design / 2023

# **Shu - Te University Taiwan**

Bachelor's Degree in Fashion Design / 2013

# **Professional Experiences**

## **Digital Designer**

## Golden Matrix Group Inc. / Dec 2024 - Current

Golden Matrix Group Inc. is a gaming technology company that develops online gaming IP and scalable white-label social gaming platforms.

Applied user-centered design principles to develop UI design and branding for the company. This included creating reusable design components in Figma for social media posts, animations, pitch deck templates, and website design, ensuring consistency across all platforms.

# **UX Designer**

#### Whitetower / Dec 2024 - Mar 2023

Whitetower is a company specialising in technical strategy, web development, design, and digital marketing.

Collaborated with a senior designer to design a client's website, applying user-centered design principles to enhance usability and visual consistency. Worked on website design, branding, and logo creation using Figma. Developed reusable design components and adapted the design for seamless implementation on WordPress and Shopify.

# **UI/UX Designer**

#### Neon Road Events / Aug 2023 - Nov 2023

Neon Road Events is an event planning and management company.

Implemented NNN heuristic principles and user-centered design approaches to redesign the company website. This involved creating reusable and tokenized design components in Figma, which were then utilized to develop the final website on Wix.

# **Graphic Designer**

#### Gadget Gang HK / Dec 2022 - Feb 2023

A YouTube channel offering in-depth tech reviews and insights on the latest innovations.

Utilised brand refinement to redesign the company's image, including a new logo, business card designs, and dynamic intro/outro animations using Illustrator, Photoshop, and After Effects, resulting in a successful increase of over 50% in audience reach.

## Volunteer

## **UI/UX Designer**

#### Australia Career Forum incorporated / Nov 2023 - Current

A Taiwanese community hosts events offering career advice and networking opportunities, aimed at fostering social connections and professional growth.

Collaborated with fellow designers to craft the UI for the company website, culminating in the creation of design components and a prototype using Figma, seamlessly handed off to developers for implementation onto the website.

#### **Awards**

## **Best Prototype Runner up**

UTS Tech Festival - Prototype and robotics showcase / 2022

## **Presentations / Project Exhibitions**

## South by Southwest (SXSW) Sydney 2023

Presented project on "Games" at the SXSW in Sydney, Australia, Oct 2023.

## **POWERHOUSE LATE X GAMING 2023**

Presented project on "Gaming" at the POWERHOUSE LATE X GAMING in Sydney, Australia, Sep 2023.

## **UTS Tech Festival 2023**

Presented project on "Game Design" at the UTS Tech Festival in Sydney, Australia, July 2023.

#### **UTS Tech Festival 2023**

Presented project on "Interaction Design Prototype" at the UTS Tech Festival in Sydney, Australia, June 2023.

#### **UTS Tech Festival 2022**

Presented project on "Prototype and robotics" at the UTS Tech Festival in Sydney, Australia, July 2022.

## **Skills**



#### **Tools**



#### Referees

Available upon request